So I gave the cookies
you made to Fawn and the kids,
and they couldn't believe it.
They were delicious! But I digress.
Tremble, puny earthlings!
One day, my race will destroy you all.
Could one of you guys get that?
It's a doorbell baby!
Hello, little guy. You know,
I was abandoned as a baby, too.
- So...
- Garbage, huh? I'll take care of it.
Bender, stop!
- It's a baby!
- A baby what?
Ow!
Oh, it's just a card!
From the orphanarium I grew up in.
Leela, you're invited to a reunion
at Cookieville Minimum-Security
Orphanarium.
Please stand clear
of self-destructing basket.
A reunion at your old orphanarium, eh?
- You gonna go?
- No way, Josébot.
I never want to see
those other orphans again.
Not after the way they used to pick on me.
One Eye, One Eye, One Eye!
Nice depth perception, One Eye!
How can you make fun of me, Kirk?
You're blind!
My eyes may not work,
but at least I got two of them.
Aw, that's terrible, Leela.
But imagine the look on their faces
when you show up with two friends
who eat all the hors d'oeuvres.
Well, I wouldn't mind rubbing my success
in a few choice faces.
Set a course for adventure!
- Ew!
- What a dump!
Just like old times.
Gosh, the bars on the windows seemed
so much thicker back then.
Mr. Vogel? Remember me?
Leela!
You're worthless,
and no one will ever love you!
You used to say that all the time.
Oh, those were happier days.
Mmm!
The "gristle in a blanket" isn't half bad.
And try one of these Popsicle sticks.
They've absorbed quite a bit of flavor.
Hey, look. It's our old group picture.
I don't see you anywhere.
That's me, over in Cootie-town.
Get a load
of this average-looking guy.
That's Adlai Atkins.
I used to have kind of a crush on him.
One Eye, One Eye!
- Stupid as a French guy!
- One Eye, One Eye, One Eye...
Well, it's time to say
hello to the old gang.
So? What you been up to
since you left the orphanarium?
Oh, livin' in a box,
fightin' the shakes. You?
Sellin' kidneys, teeth.
Whatever falls out of me.
And what am I up to, you ask?
Why, I'm a very successful space captain.
- Oh...
- Wow.
How nice for you, Leela.
That's so good for a person with one eye.
Hey! You can't feel sorry for me.
I'm a space captain,
and you're a bunch of losers.
Right. Right. We're the losers.
Well, if it isn't old One Eye?
Oh, yeah? Well, shut up, Cane Boy!
He can't hear you. He's deaf now.
Leave Leela alone.
She's leading a perfectly normal life.
She's not gussied up, duded out,
getting down, or where it's at.
Now, run along.
Thanks, Adlai.
I guess you never really
outgrow being an eyeball...
Oddball.
Nonsense, you're a space captain.
That's a fine, conventional profession.
Well, you know.
It's just for a package delivery service.
Ah, ah! A package is just
a box until it's delivered.
Huh. I'd never thought of it that way.
So what do you do these days?
Oh, I'm a doctor.
A tall doctor, you say.
Sir? You seem pretty stable.
Have you thought about adopting a kid?
Sure haven't.
Well, keep adoption in mind.
It's a great way to have a kid
without having sex.
Really?
Plus, the government will help out
with a small stipend of $100 a week.
$100 a week?
I'm so sorry I teased you back then.
Let me make it up to you.
I can fix it so no one
ever makes fun of you again.
You mean, by beating them up?
Because I've broken that blind kid's nose,
like, 10 times,
and it doesn't make a difference.
No, I specialize in phaser eye surgery.
I can build you a paraffin eye
and graft it on with skin from your foot.
It won't be able to see, but you'll look
like a perfectly normal, two-eyed person.
Me? Perfectly normal?
Mmm...
Sons, daughters, meet Uncle Fry.
Hey, why are those kids following you?
Do you have candy stuck to your ass?
No, it's called "parenting."
Come on, dumplings.
We've got 12 government stipends
to collect.
- Yeah!
- Our daddy's a giant toy!
Phaser eye surgery
is a capital idea.
I'm sure Leela's tired of morons
gaping at her eye all the time.
Oh...
I think cosmetic surgery's great, Leela.
I used to be too cute,
so I had cuteness reduction surgery,
here and here.
You guys are crazy.
Leela doesn't need surgery.
You look great the way you are.
Oh, that's so sweet, Fry.
But for once in my life,
I just want to look normal.
But you're better than normal.
You're abnormal.
If you ask me, you shouldn't
care what other people think.
You're right!
I'll start by not caring what you think.
I'm getting the surgery!
- That-a-girl!
- Right on!
- Good call.
- Wonderful.
And while you're under the knife,
you could also get an ink pouch
to help you escape your enemies.
That's the stupidest idea I've ever heard,
you imbecile.
Now, we'll find out
if the operation was a success.
Hold onto your hats.
Oh, I'm sorry. This is the wrong patient.
Whoops!
Leela, those eyes look so great on you.
Bah! I think she looked fine before.
- No!
- Wrong.
Wow! Look at me!
Although I don't have
the hang of blinking yet.
You'll get it.
Personally, I try not to blink too much
because it seems flashy.
But when I do, I enjoy it.
I did it! I blunk!
And just in time
to screw up this picture I took.
Hooray!
Pretty woman
Walkin' down the street
Ow, ow, ow...
The kind I like to meet
Pretty woman
I don't believe you
You're not the truth
No one could look as good as you
Mercy
Pretty woman
I've never felt so unremarkable!
Today, I actually blended in with a crowd!
Kids, meet the jerkbags I work with.
Hello, jerkbags!
Oh, they're so cute! What are their names?
Kids have names?
My name is Nina, and his name's Albert...
And from now on,
you're all named Bender, Jr!
Looky here.
My first government stipend check.
Twelve baby humans, 1,200 wing-wangs.
Daddy Bender, we're hungry.
What is it with you kids?
Every other day, it's food, food, food!
Oh, fine. I'll get you some stupid food.
Could we have Bender Burgers again?
No! The cat shelter's on to me.
Hello, Leela.
I was at a nearby tailor, getting one
of my Hawaiian shirts toned down,
so I thought I'd drop in
for your follow-up exam.
Oh! That's so handsome of you.
Just follow the light with your eyes.
Perfect.
You know, a guy could fall
head over heels for a gal like you.
As for me, I'm somewhat interested myself.
What are you saying?
I've never been good with words,
which is why I'm in
such a delicate conundrum.
- Will you go out with me this Sunday?
- Sure!
I don't know what else to say,
so I'll just say it.
Okeydokey, see you then.
This is so unfair. I liked you back
when you were a Cyclops.
That guy's only interested
now that you have two eyes.
You're just jealous.
No, I'm not!
Oh, wait, I am!
But my point remains valid.
Fry, I just want to try
dating a normal man,
who, if you go somewhere with him,
no one says he's crummy.
I think I deserve that once in life.
Be careful with that Adlai, Leela.
He's a doctor. They're very poor.
Actually, most doctors are rich.
What? When did this happen?
You're joking, right?
That's not funny!
Okay, they got everything you need here.
Booze, a couple of peanuts...
They got a crapper in the back.
That's one of the things
you kids do, right?
- Yeah!
- Then knock yourself out.
Hey! Hey!
Only eat and drink enough
to barely keep yourselves alive.
I'm tryin' to make a profit here.
Daddy, Bethany's hitting me!
Here.
These kids yours?
- Yeah.
- Ooh.
I'm attracted to
a man with responsibility.
That's me, baby.
Let me just ditch the kids in an alley,
and we can go have some fun.
- Daddy Bender?
- Son?
Daddy's tryin' to score
with a cheap floozy right now,
so he needs you to cram a Tinkertoy in it.
I love you, Daddy Bender.
Hey! What the hell are you doin'?
- Quit huggin' me.
- I guess you're busy.
I'll catch you later.
You morons!
I don't know what you're tryin' to pull,
but I got half a mind to hug each
and every one of you
and see how you like it!
- Yeah!
- Argh...
Come on.
Argh!
I thought I'd take you someplace ordinary.
- A place no one could object to.
- That sounds wonderful.
I'd like an extra-beautiful bouquet,
for my extra-gorgeous sweetheart.
Average, please.
Oh, Adlai,
I've had a wonderful time today.
No one's stared at me,
or avoided staring at me,
or tried to burn me.
You make me feel so not weird.
Leela, you're 999,999 in a million.
Thanks for comin' out
to get to know my boyfriend.
Isn't he dreamy?
Totally.
Listen. I just want you all to know,
your Leela's one standard lady.
Oh, Adlai! Stop.
What's so wonderful
about Leela being normal?
The rest of us aren't normal,
and that's what makes us great.
Like Dr. Zoidberg.
He's a weird monster who smells
like he eats garbage, and does.
Damn right!
And the professor's
a senile, amoral crackpot.
Hermes is a Rastafarian accountant.
Tally me banana!
Amy's a klutz from Mars.
Oops!
And, Fry, you've got that brain thing!
I already did.
So, Leela, do you want to be like us?
Or do you want to be like Adlai,
with no severe mental or social
problems whatsoever?
That's the dumbest question I ever heard.
- She's right!
- No doubt!
- Duh!
- Daylight come.
Comin' through. Watch your head.
Help! I'm under attack!
Remember your manners, kids.
Forks go in the left pocket,
spoons in the right.
Which one of you cutie muffins
gets the children's spicy squab?
Me!
What do we say
when someone gives you something?
- 'Bout time!
- That's my boy!
And here's your check. Bam!
I gotta go poopy.
You should've gone poopy before
it was time to run out on the check!
Come on! Go! Go! Through the kitchen!
You little crooks! If I catch you,
I'm gonna make cutie muffin gumbo!
You know,
seeing that strange robot
force 12 children to do his bidding
makes me think about kids of our own.
Us? Me? You? Kids?
That's correct. It's time
to stop living this vida bachelor loca.
Settle down and have kids.
Oh, Adlai.
This is the most beautiful
moment of my life.
Daddy Bender, I want a piggyback ride!
Daddy's tired.
Let's just have another dog pile on Fry.
Oh!
Tell us a story, Daddy Bender.
Story, story, story!
All right, fine. Gather around.
Yeah!
We wanna hear this one again.
"Bender's Arrest Record.
"By the Police.
"On March 3, at 2:00 p.m.,
"Bender was caught shoplifting."
Yeah. Show us the picture.
There he is.
Okay, kids. It's 9:00,
and you know what that means.
Daddy's sick of lookin' at ya,
so go to bed.
Aw!
The grown-ups have to talk. Come on, Ma.
Now, to figure out how much money
I'm rakin' in off those twerps.
Oh! I need a calculator.
You are a calculator.
I mean, a good calculator.
Minus the food,
the bunny rabbit wallpaper...
I'm gettin' 100 bucks a kid,
and they're costin' me 110!
There goes
my new kitchen cabinets.
I'm not sittin' through
one more PTA meeting!
The kids have got to go.
Daddy, how do I flush you?
Just go to bed!
You know, doing this jigsaw puzzle
of a pacifier factory
makes me want to have children
with you all the more.
Adlai, I was thinking.
Since we're both orphans,
maybe we should adopt a child.
Adoption? Yes, that's acceptable.
Heck, it's more than acceptable,
it's adequately satisfactory.
Hello? Imperial Dragon Restaurant?
I've got a herd of you-know-what's
for sale.
Let me check.
Oh, aren't you a cutie?
About 35 pounds.
What?
Hi, Bender. We'd like to adopt a child.
Well, you've come to the right place.
Because Honest Bender's Orphanarium
means discount orphans.
Now, little lady, what do I have to do
to send you home with 12 orphans today?
Uh, I'm afraid we only want one.
Whatever you say, chief.
I'll show you what I got in stock.
I remember this from when we were kids.
The warden would trot you out
in front of prospective parents,
and they'd judge you like a piece of meat.
- I'm Albert.
- Kind of fatty.
Then how 'bout this little number?
Purebred human. No vampire in there.
- Uh... Mmm...
- Well...
If you're strapped for cash,
you might want to consider
this irregular unit.
Cursed with a third ear,
but so full of that emotion
I understand is called "love."
One time, I did a hundred jump ropes.
Oh! I can't decide!
We're gonna have to think about it.
Okay, kids. Grown-ups gotta talk now.
Time for bed.
But it's 10:00 in the morning!
I said, hit the hay!
Oh, they're all so adorable.
Yeah. You know,
it's times like this,
I can hardly bear to let them go.
Good night, you princes of Maine!
You kings of New New England!
You're under arrest for child cruelty,
child endangerment,
depriving children of food,
selling children as food
and misrepresenting
the weight of livestock.
If you had kids of your own,
you'd understand.
Officer, would it be all right
if we adopted one of the kids?
Might as well. They're just gonna
rot in the evidence locker.
Nice ear!
Hey, Three Ears!
I've made up my mind.
Let's adopt her.
Her? But there's plenty of normal ones.
Come on, Adlai.
She could really use a mom and dad.
Ear Face! Ear Face!
Sally won the ugly race!
On the other hand,
the children bring up a good point.
- She does have an ear on her face.
- Well? So what?
She may be different,
but she still deserves a good home.
Oh, all right.
If you really want that one,
I can give her an operation
to make her acceptable.
She doesn't need an operation.
She's fine the way she is.
Oh, and I suppose
you were fine the way you were?
- Damn right I was!
- Yay!
Shut up, Fry.
Now, look, Adlai.
I'm proud to be different.
And I just wish I'd realized
that when I was her age.
I also have a tail!
Now, take me to the hospital and put
my eye back the way it was. Right now!
Why should I do that?
Listen, buddy.
By the end of the day,
one of us is gonna have one eye.
In recognition of Bender's generous gift
of 12 orphans and a government check
for 1,200 wing-wangs,
I hereby rename this building
the Bender B. Rodriguez Orphanarium.
It's good to have
the old weird-looking Leela back.
Oh, you're a true friend, Fry.
I guess there's nothing wrong
with being a little weird.
Leela, there's nothing
wrong with anything.
We'll miss you, Daddy Bender.
We know robots don't have emotions,
but we drawed you this picture.
So if you ever miss us,
even just a teeny bit,
you can look at it.
Hey, I smoke a cigar,
not a candy cane. Sheesh!
Aw...
Hey, what the... Whoa!
Get away! Come on.
I just got all the gum off of there.
Hey! Hey!
I hate you!
I hate you all!